A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Mental Hygiene Program, SG 1, Series 25 FA297
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Fellowships, 1925-1983; 2; 11 box(es)
  - Special Psychiatric Fellowships - Internists/Psychiatrists Discharged from Service - Applicants (A-L) (Box 9, Folder 131)
  - Special Psychiatric Fellowships - Internists/Psychiatrists Discharged from Service - Applicants (M-W) (Box 9, Folder 132)
  - Special Psychiatric Fellowships - Internists/Psychiatrists Discharged from Service - General and Financial Files, 1945-1947 (Box 9, Folder 133)
  - Training in Psychiatric Social Work - Akkershuys, Johanna and Bruyel, Wilhemina, 1947-1951 (Box 10, Folder 134)
  - Training in Psychiatric Social Work (Box 10, Folder 135)
    Alten, Ida - April 22, 1948-September 29, 1948 Eijsvoogel, Ada - April 22, 1948-February 9, 1951
  - Training in Psychiatric Social Work - General Files (Dutch Fellowships) [Ongerboer], 1947-1950 (Box 10, Folder 136)
  - Training in Psychiatric Social Work (Box 10, Folder 137)
    Murchie, Isabella - August 11, 1948-October 13, 1948 Wang, Anchen - July 1, 1948-December 6, 1948
  - University of California - School of Social Welfare - Fellowships in Psychiatric Social Work - General and Financial Files, 1942-1949 (Box 10, Folder 138)
  - University of California - School of Social Welfare - Fellowships in Psychiatric Social Work - General and Financial Files, 1942-1949 (Box 10, Folder 139)
  - University of California - School of Social Welfare - Fellowships in Psychiatric Social Work - General and Financial Files, 1942-1949 (Box 10, Folder 140)
  - University of California - School of Social Welfare - Fellowships in Psychiatric Social Work - General and Financial Files, 1942-1949 (Box 10, Folder 141)
  - University of Chicago - School of Social Service Administration - Psychiatric Social Work Fellowships - Annual Reports, 1929; 1931-1940 (Box 10, Folder 142)
  - University of Chicago - School of Social Service Administration - Psychiatric Social Work Fellowships - Annual Reports, 1929; 1931-1940 (Box 10, Folder 143)
  - University of Chicago - School of Social Service Administration - Psychiatric Social Work Fellowships - Annual Reports, 1929; 1931-1940 (Box 10, Folder 144)
  - University of Chicago - School of Social Service Administration - Psychiatric Social Work Fellowships - Annual Reports, 1929; 1931-1940 (Box 10, Folder 145)
  - University of Chicago - School of Social Service Administration - Psychiatric Social Work Fellowships - Annual Reports, 1929; 1931-1940 (Box 10, Folder 146)
  - University of Chicago - School of Social Service Administration - Psychiatric Social Work Fellowships - Annual Reports, 1929; 1931-1940 (Box 10, Folder 147)
  - University of Chicago - School of Social Service Administration - Psychiatric Social Work Fellowships - Annual Reports, 1929; 1931-1940 (Box 10, Folder 148)
  - University of Chicago - School of Social Service Administration - Psychiatric Social Work Fellowships - Annual Reports, 1929; 1931-1940 (Box 10, Folder 149)
  - University of Chicago - School of Social Service Administration - Psychiatric Social Work Fellowships - Annual Reports, 1929; 1931-1940 (Box 10, Folder 150)
  - University of Chicago - School of Social Service Administration - Psychiatric Social Work Fellowships - Annual Reports, 1929; 1931-1940 (Box 10, Folder 151)
  - University of Chicago - School of Social Service Administration - Psychiatric Social Work Fellowships - Annual Reports, 1929; 1931-1940 (Box 10, Folder 152)
  - University of Chicago - School of Social Service Administration - Psychiatric Social Work Fellowships - Annual Reports, 1929; 1931-1940 (Box 10, Folder 153)
  - University of Chicago - School of Social Service Administration - Psychiatric Social Work Fellowships - Annual Reports, 1941-1948 (Box 11, Folder 154)
  - University of Chicago - School of Social Service Administration - Psychiatric Social Work Fellowships - Annual Reports, 1941-1948 (Box 11, Folder 155)
  - University of Chicago - School of Social Service Administration - Psychiatric Social Work Fellowships - Annual Reports, 1941-1948 (Box 11, Folder 156)
  - University of Chicago - School of Social Service Administration - Psychiatric Social Work Fellowships - Annual Reports, 1941-1948 (Box 11, Folder 157)
  - University of Chicago - School of Social Service Administration - Psychiatric Social Work Fellowships - Annual Reports, 1941-1948 (Box 11, Folder 158)
  - University of Chicago - School of Social Service Administration - Psychiatric Social Work Fellowships - Annual Reports, 1941-1948 (Box 11, Folder 159)
  - University of Chicago - School of Social Service Administration - Psychiatric Social Work Fellowships - Annual Reports, 1941-1948 (Box 11, Folder 160)
  - University of Chicago - School of Social Service Administration - Psychiatric Social Work Fellowships - General and Financial Correspondence, 1930-1949 (Box 11, Folder 161)
  - University of Chicago - School of Social Service Administration - Psychiatric Social Work Fellowships - General and Financial Correspondence, 1930-1949 (Box 11, Folder 162)
  - University of Chicago - School of Social Service Administration - Psychiatric Social Work Fellowships - General and Financial Correspondence, 1930-1949 (Box 11, Folder 163)
  - University of Chicago - School of Social Service Administration - Psychiatric Social Work Fellowships - General and Financial Correspondence, 1930-1949 (Box 11, Folder 164)
  - University of Chicago - School of Social Service Administration - Psychiatric Social Work Fellowships - General and Financial Correspondence, 1930-1949 (Box 11, Folder 165)
  - University of Chicago - School of Social Service Administration - Psychiatric Social Work Fellowships - General and Financial Correspondence, 1930-1949 (Box 11, Folder 166)
  - University of Chicago - School of Social Service Administration - Psychiatric Social Work Fellowships - General and Financial Correspondence, 1930-1949 (Box 11, Folder 167)
  - University of Chicago - School of Social Service Administration - Psychiatric Social Work Fellowships - General and Financial Correspondence, 1930-1949 (Box 11, Folder 168)
  - University of Chicago - School of Social Service Administration - Psychiatric Social Work Fellowships - General and Financial Correspondence, 1930-1949 (Box 11, Folder 169)
  - University of Colorado - Psychopathic Hospital Fellowships - General and Financial Correspondence, 1931-1950 (Box 12, Folder 170)
  - University of Colorado - Psychopathic Hospital Fellowships - General and Financial Correspondence, 1931-1950 (Box 12, Folder 171)
  - University of Colorado - Psychopathic Hospital Fellowships - General and Financial Correspondence, 1931-1950 (Box 12, Folder 172)
  - University of Colorado - Psychopathic Hospital Fellowships - General and Financial Correspondence, 1931-1950 (Box 12, Folder 173)
  - University of Colorado - Psychopathic Hospital Fellowships - General and Financial Correspondence, 1931-1950 (Box 12, Folder 174)
  - University of Colorado - Psychopathic Hospital Fellowships - General and Financial Correspondence, 1931-1950 (Box 12, Folder 175)
  - University of Colorado - Psychopathic Hospital Fellowships - General and Financial Correspondence, 1931-1950 (Box 12, Folder 176)
  - University of Colorado - Psychopathic Hospital Fellowships - General and Financial Correspondence, 1931-1950 (Box 12, Folder 177)
  - University of Colorado - Psychopathic Hospital Fellowships - General and Financial Correspondence, 1931-1950 (Box 12, Folder 178)
  - Western Reserve University - School of Applied Social Sciences - Fellowships in Psychiatric Social Work - General and Financial Correspondence, 1929-1949 (Box 12, Folder 179)
  - Western Reserve University - School of Applied Social Sciences - Fellowships in Psychiatric Social Work - General and Financial Correspondence, 1929-1949 (Box 12, Folder 180)
  - Western Reserve University - School of Applied Social Sciences - Fellowships in Psychiatric Social Work - General and Financial Correspondence, 1929-1949 (Box 12, Folder 181)
  - Western Reserve University - School of Applied Social Sciences - Fellowships in Psychiatric Social Work - General and Financial Correspondence, 1929-1949 (Box 12, Folder 182)
  - Western Reserve University - School of Applied Social Sciences - Fellowships in Psychiatric Social Work - General and Financial Correspondence, 1929-1949 (Box 12, Folder 183)
  - Western Reserve University - School of Applied Social Sciences - Fellowships in Psychiatric Social Work - General and Financial Correspondence, 1929-1949 (Box 12, Folder 184)
  - Western Reserve University - School of Applied Social Sciences - Fellowships in Psychiatric Social Work - General and Financial Correspondence, 1929-1949 (Box 12, Folder 185)
  - Western Reserve University - School of Applied Social Sciences - Fellowships in Psychiatric Social Work - General and Financial Correspondence, 1929-1949 (Box 12, Folder 186)
  - Western Reserve University - School of Applied Social Sciences - Fellowships in Psychiatric Social Work - General and Financial Correspondence, 1929-1949 (Box 12, Folder 187)
- Special Projects, 1942-1951; 3; 3 box(es)
  - American Association of Psychiatric Social Workers - Educational Secretary - General and Financial Correspondence; Reports, 1947-1951 (Box 13, Folder 188)
  - American Association of Psychiatric Social Workers - Educational Secretary - General and Financial Correspondence; Reports, 1947-1951 (Box 13, Folder 189)
  - American Association of Psychiatric Social Workers - Educational Secretary - General and Financial Correspondence; Reports, 1947-1951 (Box 13, Folder 190)
  - Center for Psychiatric Orientation of Practicing Physicians - Psychotherapy in General Practice - Pilot Course at University of Minnesota - Correspondence, 1945-1946 (Box 13, Folder 191)
  - Center for Psychiatric Orientation of Practicing Physicians - Psychotherapy in General Practice - Pilot Course at University of Minnesota - Correspondence, 1945-1946 (Box 13, Folder 192)
  - Center for Psychiatric Orientation of Practicing Physicians - Psychotherapy in General Practice - Pilot Course at University of Minnesota - Correspondence, 1945-1946 (Box 13, Folder 193)
  - Center for Psychiatric Orientation of Practicing Physicians - Psychotherapy in General Practice - Pilot Course at University of Minnesota - Correspondence, 1945-1946 (Box 13, Folder 194)
  - Center for Psychiatric Orientation of Practicing Physicians - Psychotherapy in General Practice - Pilot Course at University of Minnesota - Correspondence, 1945-1946 (Box 13, Folder 195)
  - Center for Psychiatric Orientation of Practicing Physicians - Psychotherapy in General Practice - Pilot Course at University of Minnesota - Correspondence, 1945-1946 (Box 13, Folder 196)
  - Center for Psychiatric Orientation of Practicing Physicians - Psychotherapy in General Practice - Pilot Course at University of Minnesota - Correspondence, 1945-1946 (Box 13, Folder 197)
  - Center for Psychiatric Orientation of Practicing Physicians - Psychotherapy in General Practice - Pilot Course at University of Minnesota - Correspondence, 1945-1946 (Box 13, Folder 198)
  - Center for Psychiatric Orientation of Practicing Physicians - Psychotherapy in General Practice - Pilot Course at University of Minnesota - Course Comments, April 1-13, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 199)
  - Center for Psychiatric Orientation of Practicing Physicians - Psychotherapy in General Practice - Pilot Course at University of Minnesota - Follow-up Correspondence, 1946-1949 (Box 13, Folder 200)
  - Center for Psychiatric Orientation of Practicing Physicians - Psychotherapy in General Practice - Pilot Course at University of Minnesota - Follow-up Correspondence, 1946-1949 (Box 13, Folder 201)
  - Center for Psychiatric Orientation of Practicing Physicians - Psychotherapy in General Practice - Pilot Course at University of Minnesota - Memoranda, 1945-1946 (Box 14, Folder 202)
  - Center for Psychiatric Orientation of Practicing Physicians - Psychotherapy in General Practice - Pilot Course at University of Minnesota - Memoranda, 1945-1946 (Box 14, Folder 203)
  - Center for Psychiatric Orientation of Practicing Physicians - Psychotherapy in General Practice - Pilot Course at University of Minnesota - Memoranda, 1945-1946 (Box 14, Folder 204)
  - Center for Psychiatric Orientation of Practicing Physicians - Psychotherapy in General Practice - Pilot Course at University of Minnesota - Memoranda, 1945-1946 (Box 14, Folder 205)
  - Center for Psychiatric Orientation of Practicing Physicians - Psychotherapy in General Practice - Pilot Course at University of Minnesota - Memoranda and Course Material, March-July; 1946 (Box 14, Folder 206)
  - Center for Psychiatric Orientation of Practicing Physicians - Psychotherapy in General Practice - Pilot Course at University of Minnesota - Memoranda and Course Material, March-July; 1946 (Box 14, Folder 207)
  - Center for Psychiatric Orientation of Practicing Physicians - Psychotherapy in General Practice - Pilot Course at University of Minnesota - "Teaching Psychotherapeutic Medicine" - Editorial Correspondence, 1946-1949 (Box 14, Folder 208)
  - Center for Psychiatric Orientation of Practicing Physicians - Psychotherapy in General Practice - Pilot Course at University of Minnesota - "Teaching Psychotherapeutic Medicine" - Editorial Correspondence, 1946-1949 (Box 14, Folder 209)
  - Center for Psychiatric Orientation of Practicing Physicians - Psychotherapy in General Practice - Pilot Course at University of Minnesota - "Teaching Psychotherapeutic Medicine" - Editorial Correspondence, 1946-1949 (Box 14, Folder 210)
  - Center for Psychiatric Orientation of Practicing Physicians - Psychotherapy in General Practice - Pilot Course at University of Minnesota - "Teaching Psychotherapeutic Medicine" - Editorial Correspondence, 1946-1949 (Box 14, Folder 211)
  - Group for the Advancement of Psychiatry - General and Financial Correspondence; Reports, 1946-1948 (Box 14, Folder 212)
  - Group for the Advancement of Psychiatry - General and Financial Correspondence; Reports, 1946-1948 (Box 14, Folder 213)
  - Group for the Advancement of Psychiatry - General and Financial Correspondence; Reports, 1946-1948 (Box 14, Folder 214)
  - Group for the Advancement of Psychiatry - General and Financial Correspondence; Reports, 1946-1948 (Box 14, Folder 215)
  - Group for the Advancement of Psychiatry - General and Financial Correspondence; Reports, 1946-1948 (Box 14, Folder 216)
  - Group for the Advancement of Psychiatry - General and Financial Correspondence; Reports, 1946-1948 (Box 14, Folder 217)
  - Group for the Advancement of Psychiatry - General and Financial Correspondence; Reports, 1949-1950 (Box 15, Folder 218)
  - Group for the Advancement of Psychiatry - Report of the Committee on Medical Education - Editorial Correspondence [Geddes Smith], 1947-1948 (Box 15, Folder 219)
  - Group for the Advancement of Psychiatry - Report of the Committee on Medical Education - Editorial Correspondence [Geddes Smith], 1947-1948 (Box 15, Folder 220)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene - Division on Psychiatric Rehabilitation - Correspondence, Reports and Bulletins, 1943-1949 (Box 15, Folder 221)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene - Division on Psychiatric Rehabilitation - Correspondence, Reports and Bulletins, 1943-1949 (Box 15, Folder 222)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene - Division on Psychiatric Rehabilitation - Correspondence, Reports and Bulletins, 1943-1949 (Box 15, Folder 223)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene - Division on Psychiatric Rehabilitation - Correspondence, Reports and Bulletins, 1943-1949 (Box 15, Folder 224)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene - Division on Psychiatric Rehabilitation - Correspondence, Reports and Bulletins, 1943-1949 (Box 15, Folder 225)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene - Division on Psychiatric Rehabilitation - Correspondence, Reports and Bulletins, 1943-1949 (Box 15, Folder 226)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene - Division on Psychiatric Rehabilitation - Correspondence, Reports and Bulletins, 1943-1949 (Box 15, Folder 227)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene - Division on Psychiatric Rehabilitation - Correspondence, Reports and Bulletins, 1943-1949 (Box 15, Folder 228)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene - Report on Military Psychiatric Social Work [Elizabeth Healy Roth] - Correspondence, 1946-1948 (Box 15, Folder 229)
  - Psychiatric War Emergencies - Miscellaneous Material (A-S), 1943-1945 (Box 15, Folder 230)
  - Psychiatric War Emergencies - Miscellaneous Material (V), April-September; 1944 (Box 15, Folder 231)
  - Psychiatric War Emergencies - Miscellaneous Material (W), 1942-1943 (Box 15, Folder 232)
  - Second Postgraduate Course in Psychiatry - Pilot Course #2 at University of Minnesota - General Files and Correspondence, 1946-1947 (Box 15, Folder 233)
  - Second Postgraduate Course in Psychiatry - Pilot Course #2 at University of Minnesota - General Files and Correspondence, 1946-1947 (Box 15, Folder 234)
  - Second Postgraduate Course in Psychiatry - Pilot Course #2 at University of Minnesota - Minutes of Planning Conference, November 2, 1946; November 23, 1946 (Box 15, Folder 235)
  - Second Postgraduate Course in Psychiatry - Pilot Course #2 at University of Minnesota - Minutes of Planning Conference, November 2, 1946; November 23, 1946 (Box 15, Folder 236)
- Special Studies, 1929-1952; 4; 9 box(es)
  - California Department of Public Health - General Files and Correspondence, 1944-1949 (Box 16, Folder 237)
  - California Department of Public Health - General Files and Correspondence, 1944-1949 (Box 16, Folder 238)
  - California Department of Public Health - General Files and Correspondence, 1944-1949 (Box 16, Folder 239)
  - California Department of Public Health - General Files and Correspondence, 1944-1949 (Box 16, Folder 240)
  - Children's Hospital Boston - Pediatric-Mental Hygiene Unit - Financial Data, 1934-1943 (Box 16, Folder 241)
  - Children's Hospital Boston - Pediatric-Mental Hygiene Unit - General Files and Correspondence, 1934-1942 (Box 16, Folder 242)
  - Children's Hospital Boston - Pediatric-Mental Hygiene Unit - General Files and Correspondence, 1934-1942 (Box 16, Folder 243)
  - Children's Hospital Boston - Pediatric-Mental Hygiene Unit - General Files and Correspondence, 1934-1942 (Box 16, Folder 244)
  - Children's Hospital Boston - Pediatric-Mental Hygiene Unit - General Files and Correspondence, 1934-1942 (Box 16, Folder 245)
  - Children's Hospital Boston - Pediatric-Mental Hygiene Unit - General Files and Correspondence, 1934 May 2-1939 September 21 (Box 16, Folder 245A)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Restricted - Confidential material.
  - Columbia University-Presbyterian Medical Center - Babies Hospital Pediatric-Psychiatric Service - General Files and Correspondence, 1934-1939 (Box 16, Folder 246)
  - Columbia University-Presbyterian Medical Center - Babies Hospital Pediatric-Psychiatric Service - General Files and Correspondence, 1934-1939 (Box 16, Folder 247)
  - Columbia University-Presbyterian Medical Center - Babies Hospital Pediatric-Psychiatric Service - General Files and Correspondence, 1934-1939 (Box 16, Folder 248)
  - Columbia University-Presbyterian Medical Center - Babies Hospital Pediatric-Psychiatric Service - General Files and Correspondence, 1934-1939 (Box 16, Folder 249)
  - Gilbert, Ruth - General Files and Correspondence, January-February; 1937 (Box 16, Folder 250)
  - Harvard Medical School - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital Medical-Psychiatric Service - General Files and Correspondence, 1944-1949 (Box 17, Folder 251)
  - Harvard Medical School - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital Medical-Psychiatric Service - General Files and Correspondence, 1944-1949 (Box 17, Folder 252)
  - Harvard Medical School - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital Medical-Psychiatric Service - General Files and Correspondence, 1944-1949 (Box 17, Folder 253)
  - Harvard Medical School - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital Medical-Psychiatric Service - General Files and Correspondence, 1944-1949 (Box 17, Folder 254)
  - Harvard Medical School - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital Medical-Psychiatric Service - General Files and Correspondence, 1944-1949 (Box 17, Folder 255)
  - Harvard Medical School - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital Medical-Psychiatric Service - General Files and Correspondence, 1944-1949 (Box 17, Folder 256)
  - Joint Medico-Legal Committee - Philadelphia County Medical Society and Philadelphia Bar Association - General Files and Correspondence, 1939-1943 (Box 17, Folder 257)
  - Joint Medico-Legal Committee - Philadelphia County Medical Society and Philadelphia Bar Association - General Files and Correspondence, 1939-1943 (Box 17, Folder 258)
  - Joint Medico-Legal Committee - Philadelphia County Medical Society and Philadelphia Bar Association - General Files and Correspondence, 1939-1943 (Box 17, Folder 259)
  - Long Island College of Medicine - Department of Psychiatry - General Files and Correspondence, 1942-1945 (Box 17, Folder 260)
  - Long Island College of Medicine - Department of Psychiatry - General Files and Correspondence, 1942-1945 (Box 17, Folder 261)
  - Long Island College of Medicine - Department of Psychiatry - General Files and Correspondence, 1942-1945 (Box 17, Folder 262)
  - Long Island College of Medicine - Department of Psychiatry - General Files and Correspondence, 1942-1945 (Box 17, Folder 263)
  - Long Island College of Medicine - Department of Psychiatry - General Files and Correspondence, 1946-1949 (Box 18, Folder 264)
  - Long Island College of Medicine - Department of Psychiatry - General Files and Correspondence, 1946-1949 (Box 18, Folder 265)
  - Long Island College of Medicine - Department of Psychiatry - General Files and Correspondence, 1946-1949 (Box 18, Folder 266)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene - Study of Psychiatric Education - Financial Data, 1932-1937 (Box 18, Folder 267)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene - Study of Psychiatric Education - Financial Data, 1932-1937 (Box 18, Folder 268)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene - Study of Psychiatric Education - Financial Data, 1932-1937 (Box 18, Folder 269)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene - Study of Psychiatric Education - Financial Data, 1932-1937 (Box 18, Folder 270)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene - Study of Psychiatric Education - General Files and Correspondence, 1932-1939 (Box 18, Folder 271)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene - Study of Psychiatric Education - General Files and Correspondence, 1932-1939 (Box 18, Folder 272)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene - Study of Psychiatric Education - General Files and Correspondence, 1932-1939 (Box 18, Folder 273)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene - Study of Psychiatric Education - General Files and Correspondence, 1932-1939 (Box 18, Folder 274)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene - Study of Psychiatric Education - General Files and Correspondence, 1932-1939 (Box 18, Folder 275)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene - Study of Psychiatric Education - General Files and Correspondence, 1932-1939 (Box 18, Folder 276)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene - Study of Psychiatric Education - General Files and Correspondence, 1932-1939 (Box 18, Folder 277)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene - Study of Psychiatric Education - Reports, 1932-1933 (Box 18, Folder 278)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene - Study of Psychiatric Education - Reports, 1932-1933 (Box 18, Folder 279)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene - Study of Psychiatric Education - Reports, 1932-1933 (Box 18, Folder 280)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene - Study of Psychiatric Education - Reports, 1934 (Box 19, Folder 281)